Mark Felt: The Man Who Brought Down the White House is a drama,
history, thriller film directed by Peter Landesman.
The story of Mark Felt, who under the name "Deep Throat" helped journalists Bob
Woodward and Carl Bernstein uncover the Watergate scandal in 1974.
Mark Felt, played by Liam Neeson.
Audrey Felt, played by Diane Lane.
Joan Felt, played by Maika Monroe.
Carol Tschudy, played by Wendi McLendon-Covey.
Bob Woodward, played by Julian Morris.
Charlie Bates, played by Josh Lucas.
Mark Felt: The Man Who Brought Down the White House is a 2017 American biographical political thriller film written and
directed by Peter Landesman, and based on the 2006 autobiography of FBI agent Mark Felt, written with John O'Connor.
The film depicts how Felt became the anonymous source nicknamed "Deep Throat" for reporters Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein and helped
them in their investigation of the Watergate scandal, which resulted in the resignation of President Richard Nixon.
The film stars Liam Neeson, Diane Lane, Tony Goldwyn, and Maika Monroe.
It premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 8, and was
theatrically released on September 29, 2017, by Sony Pictures Classics.
It is also the fourth film on the Watergate scandal, following All the
President's Men (1976), The Final Days (1989), and Dick (1999).
The film explores themes of usa president, 1970s, fbi, scandal, richard nixon.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.